// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single

export const quiz ={
    topic: 'The Bible',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    perQuestionScore: 10,
    questions: [
    {
      question: 'The Gospel of Mark begins with:',
      choices: ['John the Baptist\'s birth',
      'Jesus\' birth',
      'The angel Gabriel appearing to Mary',
      'Jesus\' baptism by John'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Jesus\' baptism by John',
    },
    {
      question: 'John, the forerunner of Jesus, proclaims forgiveness of sins and performs:',
      choices: ['Circumcisions',
      'Baptisms',
       'Weddings',
      'Miracles'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Baptisms',
    },
    {
     question: 'When Jesus is baptized, the Spirit of God descends on him in the shape of:',
     choices: ['A dove',
     'Flames',
     'Angels',
     'A sunbeam'],
     type: 'MCQs',
     correctAnswer: 'A dove',
   },
   {
     question: 'All of the following figures recognize Jesus in Mark except:',
     choices: [  ' The demons',
     ' John the Baptist',
     ' The Gentile soldier at the cross',
     ' The reader of the Gospel',],
     type: 'MCQs',
     correctAnswer: 'John the Baptist',
    },
    {
      question: 'The phrase \“Jesus\' Passion\” refers to:',
      choices: [' Jesus\' birth',
      ' Jesus\' violent actions in the Temple',
      ' Jesus\' love for humanity',
      ' Jesus\' suffering'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: ' Jesus\' suffering',
    },
    {
      question: ' According to Mark, the messiah must:',
      choices: [ ' Suffer and die',
      ' Preach and baptize',
      ' Become the high priest',
      ' Take control of Israel'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: ' Suffer and die',
    },
    {
      question: ' In first-century apocalyptic Judaism, the term “Son of Man” referred to:',
      choices: [ ' God\'s son',
      ' A cosmic figure',
      ' The king',
      ' The high priest'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: ' A cosmic figure',
    },
    {
      question: 'At Jesus\' trial in Mark, the Sanhedrin charges him with:',
      choices: [ ' Theft',
      ' Blasphemy',
      ' Being empowered by Satan',
      ' Not observing Sabbath laws'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: ' Blasphemy',
    },
    {
      question: ' In Mark, the Temple curtain rips:',
      choices: ['At Jesus\' birth',
      'At Jesus\' trial',
     'At Jesus\' death',
      'At Jesus\' resurrection'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'At Jesus\' death',
    },
    {
      question: 'The Gospel of Mark was probably written around:',
      choices: [' 35 - 40 C.E.',
      ' 45-50 C.E.',
      ' 55-60 C.E.',
      ' 65-70 C.E.'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer:' 65-70 C.E.',
    },
    
    
  ]
  }